## CONTACT

Phone: 647-822-3042

E-mail: clement.sung7@gmail.com Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/clement-sung7

Site: github.com/clembrulee

Portfolio: clementsung.com

## PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

HTML5

Javascript(ES6)

React

Firehase

RESTful API

Responsive design

Website accessibility requirements

Version control using Git and Github

Paired programming

Team-based development

Project Scope Management

Microsoft Office(Word, Excel)

Labware LIMS software

Empower software

# **CLEMENT SUNG**

## FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

#### **ABOUT**

I am a front-end web developer with experience building web applications using HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Firebase and API integrations. My background as a quality control analyst has helped me develop adaptability, critical analysis, and attention to detail skills that I can apply to creating clean, responsive, and accessible web applications/solutions.

#### **PROJECTS**

## Podcast Prioritizer Live / Repo

HTML |CSS| React

Team development project

created to recommend podcasts based on a user's

travel destination

## Cratediggers Live / Repo

HTML |SCSS| Javascript
Paired programming project

created to recommend music

artists based on similar artists

or a specific genre

#### **EDUCATION**

WEB DEVELOPMENT IMMERSIVE BOOTCAMP Juno College | Apr 2021 - June 2021

JAVASCRIPT FUNDAMENTALS

Juno College | Feb 2021 - Mar 2021

INTRO TO WEB DEVELOPMENT

Juno College | Oct 2021 - Nov 2021

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN CHEMISTRY (BSC) Ryerson University | Sep 2010 - Apr 2015

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

QUALITY CONTROL ANALYST

Estee Lauder Companies Inc. | Dec 2019 - Mar 2021

- Performed analytical testing of in-process materials and raw materials on daily basis(10-15 samples per day) to meet release targets.
- Wrote comprehensive reports for out-of-specification results, deviations, and corrective and preventative action plans while managing time to perform daily analytical testing.
- Aided the team in daily routine instrument calibrations and analytical tests to maintain workflow.

### QUALITY CONTROL CHEMIST

Apotex Inc | Feb 2016 - Dec 2019

- Performed analytical chemistry, and wet chemistry tests on various drug products, an average of 12 samples, on a daily basis
- Review chemists' documented work through LIMS(laboratory information management system) software prior to releasing the product to market.
- ·Worked in a QC lab following good manufacturing practices/good laboratory practices to adhere to regulatory bodies such as Health Canada and FDA and successfully completed 4+ audits